
{
  "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "Gandalfs alias?",
        "answers":["Mithrandir", "Olorin", "Both are correct"],
        "correctAnswer": "Both are correct",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Both are correct"
      },
      {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Who changes colour during ”The Two Towers”, from Grey to White?",
        "answers":["Gandalf", "Galadriel", "Saruman],
        "correctAnswer": " Gandalf",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Gandalf"
      },
      {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "Who possesses the ring of power at the start of the trilogy?",
        "answers":["Gollum", "Bilbo", "Frodo"],
        "correctAnswer": "Bilbo",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Bilbo"
      },
      {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "When the pass of Caradhras is blocked, where does Frodo say the fellowship should go?",
        "answers":["Moria", "Celebdil", "Fanuidhol"],
        "correctAnswer": "Moria",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Moria"
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "Name Aragorn’s ancestor who failed to destroy the One Ring",
        "answers":["Eldarion", "Isildur", "Sauron"],
        "correctAnswer": "Isildur",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Isildur"
      },
      {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Who is the steward of Gondor?",
        "answers":["Boromir","Denethor", "Faramir"],
        "correctAnswer": "Denethor",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Denethor"
      },
      {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "To whom does Pippin pledge allegiance?",
        "answers":["Boromir", "Denethor", "Theoden"],
        "correctAnswer": "Denethor",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Denethor"
      },
      {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "What is the name of Gandalf’s horse?",
        "answers":["Balrog", "Shadowfax", "Galadriel"],
        "correctAnswer": "Shadowfax",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Shadowfax"
      },
      {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Where is Saruman’s tower, Orthanc, located?",
        "answers":["Minas Tirith", "Isengard", "Hobbiton"],
        "correctAnswer": " Isengard",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": " Isengard"
      },
      {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "What animal does Gollum give to Frodo?",
        "answers":["A fish", "A rabbit", "A potato"],
        "correctAnswer": "A rabbit",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "A rabbit"
      },
      {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "Where does Théoden decide to send his people?",
        "answers":["Helm’s deep", "Minas Tirith", "Rohan"],
        "correctAnswer": "Helm’s deep",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Helm’s deep"
      },
      {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "What does Elrond offer to Aragorn?",
        "answers":["A ring","A sword"],
        "correctAnswer": "A sword",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "A sword"
      },
      {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the ring destroyed at Mount Doom?",
        "answers":["It falls into lava", "It is destroyed by an Axe"],
        "correctAnswer": "It falls into lava",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "It falls into lava"
      },
      {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "In The Return of the King, who kills the Witch King?",
        "answers":["Eowyn","Gandalf","Arwen"],
        "correctAnswer": "Eowyn",
        "difficultyLevel": "Advanced",
        "description": "Eowyn"
      }
  ]
}
